It'll be impossible for us to eat all this.
Oh, there you are.
Why do you look like that?
I thought I gave you a mission to search for His Majesty.
I do not recall allowing you to rest.
What the hell was that?
My sword just fell from against the wall.
Tie that stupid thing up already.
Fallon?
Marcel. Marcel!
Where's Fallon?
Uh, what?
Hey, have you seen Fallon anywhere?
Can't say anyone's passed by.
What? Did something happen?
It can't be.
Did she leave from this window?
I'm gonna look outside.
Huh?
Why is it...
Fallon!
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you...
Are you okay? Tell me what happened.
I must find him.
I must find Lord Delgall.
Wait a sec.
How...
In this kingdom...
Everything that you can see...
Buildings...
Currency...
Livestock...
Citizens...
Blood...
And meat.
Even each and every tiny grain of sand that you crush beneath your feet.
All of it is the personal property of his majesty, King Delgall.
And only his.
Do you understand, you disgusting thief?
You.
I remember you.
You were wandering around in the paintings.
The paintings?
That's right.
But who is he?
You vile intruder.
Just what is it that you want?
It's the Lord of the Dungeon.
The Mad Mage himself.
You.
You get away from them.
Do you hear me?
I won't miss again.
You should know your place, you filth.
Hey, let's go.
Come on.
Shut up!
L-Laios!
Such amazing strength.
What the hell is going on here?
Is he an adventurer?
Spellbook?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Is that some kind of magic chant?
This chanting could only be...
Ancient magic!
To bury them all!
Explosion magic.
Abjuration magic.
No, those won't work.
Then...
I'll overwrite the spell instead.
Dispel!
This ancient magic?
I can understand it.
I can read it.
But...
I can't keep up with it!
Are you the one who made this dungeon?
I need...
To talk to you about...
I...
Don't look so worried.
The thieves are gone now.
And his majesty will soon be returning.
When he does, we'll be sure to celebrate.
Hey, dragon.
That must be inconvenient.
Let me change your form for you.
Do what you have been ordered to.
Yes.
What happened?
Hold on.
I'll get lights up.
What is this place?
Come to think of it, where did we fall from?
How do we leave?
There's no...
What's happening?
Oh, no.
Are the walls closing in?
You've got to be kidding me!
Dammit!
We've got to look for an exit!
Where?
Can't you fix it with magic or something?
And what kind of magic do you suggest?
We're dead.
This won't be my first time dying, but no one is going to find us under rocks.
We just got Fallon back.
And I was so close to the dungeon's secrets.
It'll have been for nothing.
It can't end like this.
Marcel, no!
Whoa, it's a tunnel!
Let's use it to get out!
What, we don't even know where it ends up?
It's better than becoming a pancake!
Just hurry up and go!
Where the hell are we?
Wherever it is, we've got to get out and fast.
I... I can't even move a finger right now.
You've got to get up!
If that guy finds us again, we're...
It's... it's over.
It's over.
There's no need to...
They... they disappeared?
Ugh, damn it.
I think I'm going crazy.
Senshi, I need you to wake up Lyos for me.
I'm gonna go look around a little bit.
Get him!
How did he manage to sneak in here?
The long ears with them!
There he is!
Come here, you!
Quiet down!
What's going on?
We found some moles, Captain.
How'd they get in here?
Why'd the watch not catch them?
To be honest, we don't know.
The hole's closed up now.
Whatever.
A tiny man, an underground dweller, a long legs, and a long ear.
How perfect!
I've never killed a long ear before, but now I can.
Give the small one to the dogs.
They're starved for entertainment.
Wait.
You wouldn't happen to be Chief Zone's younger sister, would you, Miss?
The reason we came here was actually to fulfill a promise with the Chief.
So mind showing us mercy?
How do you know that name?
Hold on.
We know you.
You're since way different, vegetable seller.
It must have been important for you to come this far.
What was the promise you made with him?
I see.
Things are making a lot more sense now.
I did think it was weird that the dragon didn't seem to be around anymore.
In place of my brother, I thank you.
Go prepare the medicine!
It's ready.
Oh, hey.
We were attacked by a magic-using elf earlier.
You know anything?
Like, maybe...
What did the elf look like?
Oh, uh, he had brown skin?
And silver hair?
That's him.
I can't say I know many details.
What I do know is, he was here long before we were.
And seems to rule over the dungeon.
If someone from the outside starts to meddle with the dungeon more than necessary,
then he appears.
He creates monsters and controls them.
Changes the terrain.
And can kill anything simply by opening that buck.
Wait, he rules over the dungeon?
So then, that was the mad mage?
We've caught the attention of the mad mage?
You've gotta be kidding.
Dammit, we need to get out of here now!
Did Marcel's magic call him to us?
Or is it because we killed the dragon?
He has several monsters working under him.
If you killed one of them, then you probably made him angry.
To protect us from that fate, my brother made sure to tell us never to touch the red dragon.
Brother's right about everything.
That bastard!
When they wake up, they'll definitely want to start looking for Fallon.
I need to make them give up no matter the cost.
What'll you do?
Whatever it takes.
Burn the staff to ashes.
Say we saw Fallon head for the surface.
Or tell them she was satisfied after eating the dragon meat.
So you plan to lie to him?
Of course I do!
If I don't lie, then those two idiots are never gonna give up!
If we go any further, then we're definitely gonna get killed.
Do you want to become part of the wall?
Cause I sure don't!
I...
There's absolutely no way I'm dying with those two.
Hey, uh...
I'd like to go grab what we left behind.
Would you mind taking me there?
Yes, I mind.
The stench of your cowardly nature might rub off on me.
What?
I'm asking you to...
Can you please take him back?
He is a coward, but he's not a bad person.
Senshi!
You're not coming along?
Someone needs to stay by Laios and Marcil's side.
What?
If it's coming from you, I can't argue.
I hate it, but fine.
I'll guide him there.
Damn it.
I can't believe I'm surrounded by such idiots!
So you lost a companion?
We sure did.
The last time we saw her, she had collapsed not that far from the Mad Mage.
It's hard to be optimistic.
Still no excuse to lie to the rest of your party.
It's easy when it's not your problem, huh?
I was only kidding!
Behind you.
Just relax.
They're this town's residence.
The ghosts that reside in this area are still sane, and only appear when they want to be seen.
The paths that they travel are safe.
Let's follow.
Are you serious?
Down there.
That's where we were before.
But the red dragon is gone.
Did it come back to life, maybe?
No.
The dogs don't seem to be on high alert.
The mage either took it away, or made it disappear.
It looks like there was an explosion.
A fire was lit near the dragon's fuel sack, and it exploded.
I'm shocked you survived.
One of our party members used abjuration magic and protected us.
So we were fine.
You roll with a pretty good party, don't you?
If you were there, you wouldn't be saying that.
The person who did it had no idea she could use that spell.
And later, our healer almost got us wiped out.
Sure, it eventually worked out in the end, but if it hadn't, we would have looked like real fools.
That's what I have to deal with.
By the way, how exactly did you all manage to defeat the red dragon?
Senshi and I distracted it.
And then the tall man, his name's Laios, by the way, jumped onto it and struck its weak point, which finally took the red dragon down.
That's pretty impressive.
Courageousness is a good quality for a fighter to have.
Oh, that wasn't courage.
It was fine since we succeeded, but it was a dumb gamble.
It really freaked me out.
How can these people live so recklessly like that?
We had two other party members who left our group.
Thinking about it now, seems like they were probably the smart ones.
I should have left then, but I guess I was too stubborn at the time.
So you're saying you would have been fine losing your remaining party?
It's not that.
It's more...
Maybe because I said I would tag along with him.
It made him feel like he had to commit.
Okay.
So what happened after you killed the dragon?
We healed all of our injuries and then...
We ate in here.
We cooked up a bunch of the dragon meat.
Glad to hear it.
You should enjoy the spoils of battle.
And the mage appeared shortly after your victory?
How did you all manage to survive that?
Our party's magic user.
She was able to counter the attack.
That long-eared girl?
Someone with such a dumb-looking face handled that?
Marcel really is an idiot.
She uses sketchy magic.
And even if we're able to get out of this dungeon,
who knows if she can live a normal life now?
It's not just her, though.
All of them are idiots.
Just total morons.
They think it's worth it to keep pushing themselves.
People like that?
It's impossible to convince them.
So you'll lie to them instead?
I think there's a better way to handle this.
Lying to get them to go back up to the surface
sounds like the perfect plan to me!
Perfect for a coward!
Cause if you weren't aware,
I'm more important!
That isn't what I meant.
Just be honest and tell them
that you don't want them to die.
Hm.
Damn it, what are you doing here?
You really chose to come all this way.
Although,
I guess that makes you the smartest
out of all of us.
A blood trail.
Like a dead body was dragged away.
Hey!
You coming or not?
Yeah, sorry.
Hey, I'm back
and I got our stuff.
Whoa!
The hell are you doing?
You're supposed to be laying down!
No, I'm feeling fine.
That's because your sense of pain
is off
because of the medicine!
Fallon should still be
somewhere nearby.
Please, just calm down!
I need to talk to you two.
You know,
I actually thought about it and...
Senshi, let me talk first, okay?
Laios.
Huh?
There's a lot going on in your heart
that I don't understand.
But in our current situation,
we can't continue exploring.
Someone's gonna...
die.
Laios,
I'm begging you.
Can you hold off
and return to the surface?
I really don't want to lose you guys.
I know it doesn't compare
to how you feel about your sister,
but three people are in danger here.
If we mention the Mad Mage,
the Island Lord might take action
and we can scrounge up money
and hire more people.
If we're prepared,
then we can come back
to this floor a lot faster later.
So, Laios,
please,
let's all go back to the surface.
If I'm being honest,
I only have a very small portion
of ingredients and spices
left in my stock.
I'd like Fallon to eat
some good meals
whenever we see her again.
so I'm all for returning to town
and restocking.
I sent a message out
about the Red Dragon.
Brothers should return
with the others eventually.
Once you finish
all of your preparations
and come back
to this settlement again,
we will do the best we can
to support your party.
All right.
I'm sorry that I worried you all.
Let's pack up and head back.
Yeah.
jury.
Bye.
vii's君 of the best way
for taking a picway
by going into a power
in an open Roman
enter the house
up in red
and everyone
겼
they często
sent me
near the security
and go there!
Bye!